# 最近我们这口罩不是特别好买
Recently, it has been difficult to buy masks in our region.
# 所以说自己准备做一个
So, I decided to make one for myself.
# 这个铁口罩，已经做完了
This iron mask is finished.
# 这是全封闭式的
This mask is fully sealed.
# 通气的来源
The venting
# 是我身后的这个小氧气瓶
comes from this little oxygen bottle.
# 美观而又方便
It is both convenient and aesthetic.
# 可以随身携带
And it is portable.
# 下面我们用烟雾测试一下它的封闭性
Let's use smoke to test out its sealing abiltiy.
# 可以看出我在烟雾中挺淡定
See, I look quite calm in the smoke.
# 烟雾越来越浓
As the smoke gets stronger,
# 但是我依然这么淡定
I still remain calm.
# 连声咳嗽都没有咳嗽
I didn't even cough.
# 这足以证明，它的封闭性是非常的强的
This is enough to prove how sealed this mask is.
# 有了这个铁口罩，我们就可以减少粉尘和细菌的危害
With this mask, we can reduce the harm caused by dust and bacteria.
# 老弟玩游戏的时候
When my younger brother was playing video games,
# 手机发热比较严重
his phone gets hot quite seriously.
# 所以我准备给老弟做一个手机散热器
So I have decided to make a cooling device for him.
# 下面为大家演示一下这个怎么用
Let me show you how to use this.
# 首先把手机放在这个上面来
First, we need to put our phone on top.
# 把这个肩键安装上
And put those two buttons on.
# 然后
Then,
# 打开开关
open the switch.
# 安装到背部
And put this on the back.
# 然后把循环泵也插上
Finally, we will plug in the pump.
# 加上水的冷却，加上风冷
With both water cooling and wind cooling,
# 这样我们玩手机的时候
his phone
# 就不会
won't
# 手机就不会发烫了
get hot when playing video games.
# 下面我让老弟体验一下效果怎么样
Now, I will let my brother try this new cooling device.
# 用的怎么样，老弟？
How is it?
# 感觉不错，非常完美
It's perfect!